# ZUBAIRU MUSA

# FRONTEND WEB DEVELOPER

## CONTACT

+23

+2348033697939

 $\bowtie$ 

zubairuzb2@gmail.com



22 K/Kibo Zaria - Kaduna

-----

# SKILLS

- React Js
- JavaScript
- Bootstrap
- Chakra UI
- Tailwind Css
- HTML & CSS
- SQL
- Git/Github
- PHP
- Figma
- MS Excel

# EDUCATION

BLIS

# Ahmadu Bello University, Zaria

2020-2022

Information Technology & Communication

## **Informatics Academy**

2016-2017

-----

# LANGUAGES

English

Hausa

#### PROFILE

Experienced Frontend Developer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry with front-end framework like React Js 2+. Skilled in HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, React Js, Chakra UI, Tailwind, Material UI, PHP, MySQL, etc. Adaptive to learning new technologies and focusing to solve real-world business problems with Technology.

## EXPERIENCE

# **Fullstack Developer (Intern)**

Kad ICT HUB - Kaduna

Mar 2023 - June 2023

- Design and Development of users Login, Registration, and Dashboard page using PHP, MySQL, CSS, Tailwind CSS, Material Design, HTML.
- Mentor other Frontend Developers to design beautiful responsive webpages.

## **React is Developer**

Pinnacle ICT Solutions - Zaria

June 2022 - Dec. 2022

• Building user interface of web apps using React JS and Chakra UI

# Web Developer

Sulbasoft Global ltd.

May 2021 - June. 2022

• I am responsible for designing of beautiful responsive Webpages using HTML, CSS, Javascript, Bootstrap.

## **Data Analyst**

Achesa Agric. Consult & Investment

Jan 2021 - April. 2021

- $\bullet\,\,$  Developing an ODK form using Ona form and Ms-Excel for farmers registration
- Analyzing the registration data so that the company can make an informed decision

## Links

- \* Github: https://github.com/zubairuzb
- \* QRCode Generator: https://qrcode-generator-zb.netlify.app/
- \* Advice App: https://advice-app-zb.netlify.app/
- \* Landing Page: https://dropoutscollege.netlify.app/

## References

Sulaiman Bala Sunusi CEO: Sulbasoft Global ltd. 07020567583

Mr. Jibril Muhammad Senior Software Engr. - Kad Ict Hub 08184018469